Hello everyone!
This is Hitomi Takamatsu and
I'm Maika Sasaki!
Yes, I'm Maika Sasaki! This is the second half of the video from Boat Race Miwako!
This is the second half of the video!
In the first step, we had dinner
And then, I predicted the race.
But in a hurry, I decided to do this Boat Race Splash Battle
VR... I'm going to do it!
Yay! I'm so happy!
And! I got to wear a shampoo outfit again!
I got to wear a shampoo outfit!
So cool!
It's so cool!
Maika is in the first boat because our member color is white.
It's so good!
So cool!
White is also really cool!
I don't know, it's different from the other day.
What? You got a new outfit?
I'd really like to have a splash battle with you.
If one of us finishes in the top three...
I'm going to have to eat dinner after this.
Oh, my gosh!
It's going to be gorgeous! So...
But we just practiced.
I did!
I'm so heavy.
I was in first place.
I did a monkey turn.
It's better to be stiff.
You've got that down to a science?
Yes, I think so.
I was in sixth place earlier.
One lap down.
Maybe next time we can do it.
I can do it! I can do it!
Let's get on with it!
Let's go for it!
Here are the opponents!
They look so strong!
Padri Padwar
What's paddling?
Now, we have a high-profile race for the six selected contestants.
They've been chosen.
So, six chosen.
Because they're the chosen six?
Excuse me.
How many courses?
Four courses!
Six!
Course six!
I just won on the six.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
That's a good one!
That's good.
Now!
Yes! Yes!
I just herbed the right side of the car!
Aah! Who hit me! Who hit me!
You've got to be kidding me! I'm serious!
I'll never forgive you! I'll never forgive you!
I'll never forgive you for bumping into me!
I'll never forgive you! I'm so mad!
Hey!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no! Oh, no!
I'm in.
Oh, shit.
Is it good?
Yay!
That's great!
I'll never forgive you.
Yay!
It's a tiny store... Really?
I'm a genius!
I might have a love life!
You're number one!
That'll be five for dinner!
Thank you so much!
I'm so happy!
Thank you so much for the delicious meat blotches!
Thank you so much!
So here we are at Kanayoshi-san, a 10-minute drive from Boat Race Biyako-san!
Yes, so in the VR battle, Hayaka came in first place, and I came in second place.
Today, we will have Omige's sukiyaki! I'm so happy!
I love sukiyaki! Is it okay? What's so good about it?
Thank you so much! I'm just happy, happy, happy.
Thank you very much!
I'll put the dishes on the table.
Oh, my God! It's amazing!
Can I take a picture?
Oh, my God!
That's Satamaro's sweetheart wallet!
Heh!
There you go.
Wow!
Smells great.
Oh, yeah.
Meat
Oh, wow.
Sounds good
I'm so happy.
Here you go.
Oh, man!
Wow!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Bon appétit!
Yum!
It's too good!
The meat is so delicious!
Seriously tender!
I'll add salt.
Japanese adoptive mother
Can I put it in?
Yes, please.
It really tastes different from the sukiyaki I've had before.
It's different.
It's my first time tasting it.
I tried it for the first time today at the boat race track.
It was fun.
I guess it's like anything else.
It's the most fun to see it right in front of your eyes.
Yes, it's important to be right in front of it.
But it's not the same when it's right in front of you.
It was frustrating.
This place is just too far over there.
I know.
I guess that's the way it's supposed to be.
I want to go back to the octopus.
So I really want you to learn
How to buy.
I'm good at formations
and my full strength.
If I can do that kind of thing
I'll probably get it all right.
I don't know if I can do that.
And I'm pretty sure that one and two
There's like a super tickle release.
It depends on the water.
So I'd like to go back there.
I'm sure it'll be a tick-tock release.
But I lost all the races.
But I've only done three races.
I'm always doing, like, six races or something.
This time it was a little less.
It's like a reward.
I'm just eating.
I'm really just eating.
I'm just feeling a little bit like this.
I'm going to continue to enjoy it after this.
Bon appétit.
Thank you very much.
Yes, so...
I finished eating five races.
It was delicious.
It was so good.
Great day.
It was a lot of fun.
I can't wait to see what's in store for the rest of you!
Equal Love Boat Race
I hope to keep on winning!
I knew it last time.
because of Zama Ice.
When you go to Zama Ice.
I'd like to go there. Continue.
I want to go there.
I'd love to see you all again.
I'd love it if you could watch the video.
Thank you for watching today.
Bye-bye.